From the shadows of the subconscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche
Awakens, crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack, you smooth mystical.
Yo welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, truce
Droping spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping Lenore's on guard tricks bringing love Lola Rudy Marbles fan from above
Like the away can't step in the flame. We call your truth. We say your name. It's wow
That's real. It's so big play now grab your tea and slay the dead like the away can't don't look away
Your shadows talking it came to stay we laugh we cry we speak we scream live from the madness. This ain't no dream
Hey everybody, just a little pre-show announcement.
Okay, Canada Dry, you have been timed out
for 24 hours preemptively.
Can you let him know when he comes back in?
Hi guys, how are you doing?
Hopefully you're having a great day.
Had a good sleep today
business in it's a beta a lot and
this
Haven't a pretty nice day. How are you? Good to see everybody. I
Got a hammers with some baguette
I got a couple strong coffees
Thank you guys. Thank you so much
Some damn good coffees
How's everyone doing?
So I got some new Jacks. I got this celestial tarot deck. It's really nice
I thought it was a little faded, but it has actually nice really nice colors
I like to stick like teal kind of pinkish color
Let's have a nice shuffle.
You can do a collective reading
that anybody wants a private reading
or a personal reading or a person will just ask your question.
Let me know.
What do you got?
Give me three of wands.
Three of wands, often it's a third party situation.
You're involved in, but this is kind of like
more of a one that is a good third party situation.
You know, you're bringing somebody in
To the other to the group
Maybe some extra extra or talent that is not represented. Okay. Let's see what else we got three or ones working together with somebody on what
Okay nine of stores maybe this is like you've been helping somebody
Calm down relax a little bit somebody that might be have sleepless nights or some anxiety
Even helping somebody out. It's always good to help people
So this is the the nine of stores traditionally. This is like the getting some rest rest part, okay?
Need some rest and some good rest. I got some today
It's seven of stores
I want to watch out for you know seven of sorts traditionally at someone trying to steal something a thief
Keep your eyes on your on your valuables your belongings
And any suspicious people that you might see right?
for the warning
Damn good coffee
Do a couple more in the words of advice. This is a general collective. You might resonate with anybody
Okay, now we got the six of stores, too
Vanticizing if you're if you're having trouble sleeping, you know
There are things you can do like counting sheep or beginning you're going down a merry-go-round
Yeah, this might resonate with anybody
The six and nine stores
Again, we have the three of wands popping out
Working with somebody maybe on it seems to me like something I sound like I'm stoned
I'm a little bit stoned. I'm a little bit stoned. I'm drinking some coffee right now
Right waking up a little bit. Hi guys
Very tasty, how are you guys doing?
Okay, then we have the moon card. I think the moon is like the moon is like the advice for the moon card is
There may be illusions that play, you know wait for the moon to go through some phases and things will be
Will be revealed. I think Jimmy is cute. I guess I'm groovy Jimmy
Not he's not like disagreeable to me
Remember when he came and took off his shirt on my show does that remember that?
And I've also, I've also speedo-bombed him.
Yeah, groovy, Jimmy.
Ah, really, my type.
Hi, guys.
You know,
I'm eating some really nice-looking men on TikTok.
Some very nice men
that are kind of my type.
Speedo-bomb was comedy gold, oh, thank you.
Did you see that one?
Know it is clips. I think I think it's on my discord. I think I remember that
Gosh, I am chugging this coffee
The first sip. Oh my god, I just started it. It's already almost gone
Yeah, so how is your week going guys today's Wednesday July 30th? We're almost tomorrow's 30 days past September April
So tomorrow has that 31st, right?
So we have August 1st on this Friday,
so we're just getting to the end of the month.
Let me get my other deck, this is the new deck I have,
it's really cool, it's called the,
this is called the Believe in Your Own Magic deck.
Okay, I'm gonna do some cards for everybody here.
These are quite feminine oriented,
but I do like them a lot.
Okay.
So we got for the chat. This is for the everybody. This one says voyage or voyage
It says you already have all the answers
So remember, you know, she has a map right there
There's the map is kind of like the answer key, but you know all the answers are out there
You don't know something, you know, maybe as chat GPT even if it's like a strange question sometimes even chat GPT might have
Interesting perspective on things the answers are out there. You know all the answers are out there. It's just
Are you asking the right question?
What else do we have?
We have the storm.
Every hurricane comes to an end.
So if you're going through a rough time right now,
just remember, is this the temporary rough time?
They seem like the winds have picked up
and it's like, you know,
you're holding onto your crown a little bit.
Just keep a little bit and have faith that, you know,
you have the strength to get through
just a little bit of wind, right?
What else have we got for the chat?
So are your strings being pulled by somebody else? No, you want to take control of your own narrative
You know, you want to be the hand you want to be like the big hand directing that the body, right?
You want to be you don't want somebody else's hand on hand on your wheel, right?
Even if you do like people to drive sometimes
Get a couple more cars from these thick. It's a great deck this one. Okay. We got the voyage card again. See what else we got
This one says which justice is coming
if you have a little bit of a witch inside of you, you know, this is like more of a, you know,
she's got the heels and the hat. It should be the puppy master for Jimmy. I don't know. I heard
he has a few handlers already. I don't know. I don't know if J-Dog wants to give up the reins right
now. Finally, we have homework. It says keep yourself, take yourself out on a date.
Okay, there's a woman. She's kind of at home, but she's like, you know, opens the door. There's
Nature even if nature and God is your date, you know
However, you like to state that
like great cards
So yeah, I haven't seen groovy Jimmy in a while
He did come on show a few times. I don't know he's a little controversial
but you know, I've been threatened like oh don't have this person on don't have this person on I
still have people on nothing ever happens because I'm responsible and
The people aren't gonna
Tell me what to do, right?
Let me get my glasses.
Oh, Tony, Tony the Black Dragon.
If Tony the Black Dragon, the same as Tony.
Yeah, thank you, Sassie.
If it was Tony the Black Dragon, actually Tony the,
not Tony the Tiger, Tony the, something else.
Tony's known as something else.
Okay, I absolutely destroy this coffee. I put my people up
They all uh, I'll do a free allied yet allied master. Is that the Tony Tony the?
Tony the something. Oh, I know it's Tony the tiger
Yeah guys if you'd like to come up, you know, I will
Consider today today's sponsors because we did have the nice person sponsored for the kick and so
I'll throw that towards the sponsored show too. So thank you to the donator for that
How's everyone doing?
Yeah, so I do you have a I have a vape
Hi, hi, how are you Tony's a guy at a wheelchair from Montana? Okay?
Is it the same as that guy?
That sounds like a kind of like gaudy a little bit but gaudy is in a wheelchair in your I don't know if he's in a wheelchair
I don't you might be you might be pretending
J dog. How are you J dogs that says you don't know what you're talking about rat amiss?
So
Or with your name a rat rat amiss I
Got a new vacuum cleaner guys. It works really good
Got it on Timo
For like 20 something dollars if you were you know, you wouldn't she vacuum cleaner?
I just have a couple rooms with the carpet and I'm going to start like, you know, really thick carpet and
So this vacuum was like 20 something bucks. It works pretty damn good. I
Got able to back you up the couch. I'm doing a lot along my laundry right now
You can hear my laundry machine going my house is pretty much clean. I'm gonna kick out my other coffee
I got extra shots in these copies plus I have a ham and hand baguette. I have also some uh
Hello, paino poppers. I was eating last night. They're so good
Mr. Saki, of course you can share your stream you share my stream. Yeah, of course
Feel free to share the stream. So yesterday we had on our friend
Daddy bigness, right?
His name is Andrew and I want to thank him again. I'm gonna get I'm gonna get his episode back up
I figured out on stream yard. I can actually like edit my shows and put it back on YouTube
It saves the last 50 hours and so from now on I'll be able to just start putting my episodes back up with edited
With that with the porn bombs edited out, so I know that I have been getting for a month quite a bit
so
Yeah, how are you guys doing good to see you all you guys today?
Mr. Andrews cool, okay, so I'm gonna just do a little hit. This is my
My vape, you can see I have a nice bubble already
smoked out of it.
But I've been going pretty light on it.
Oh guys, speaking of Amazon,
I do have a thank you sassy for posting the Amazon wishes.
I was approved for Amazon's Influencer program.
You know, they just, they said connect your account
with the, where you have the most influence.
I put my YouTube account and it says I was approved.
So I will be able to put on like recommendation like I'll make me able to make these little videos for the products that I buy and just demonstrate them or, you know, just, you know, give a testimonial of these products that I bought like certain decks I'll buy on YouTube and that I would recommend.
And then I'll be able to put it on a page or an influencer page on Amazon, and that'll be cool. You know, I think I'll be able to.
Maybe recommend some things and get it kicked down a little bit
So I'll put that up as soon as I get that that that working and if you are an influencer
You can you can apply for that program to you just if you have it at YouTube a tick tock or
Instagram, I think that is like pretty popular or at least you don't have a good amount of people there
I think you probably have a good chance of getting approved for the influencer if you don't do that
You can also get the affiliate program for Amazon. Yeah, it was like I thought on on TikTok yesterday
It was like advertised like oh joy the influencer program
You're invited and so I tried and I
Was I got approved and so I'm not sure what the requirements are exactly. I just know you know
I have like 2,600 people on my YouTube channel.
So, and, you know, it qualified me.
So, if you had got a desire to maybe promote
some Amazon products, I think Amazon's awesome.
They have the best prices next to Timo.
I think Timo is pretty good too now.
The Timo, you don't know what you're getting
100% of the time.
You know, it is usually directly from a Chinese factory.
Not necessarily
100% genuine especially the tarot decks. I think these are knockoff copies of some of the tarot decks, but they are easier to shuffle
I like the I like kind of the cheaper card stock
It's just easier for me to shuffle a little bit than some even expensive sex. I bought some really hard cards that are
Can be difficult to shuffle so I'll let you see coming here. Here's how easy this is shuffle these cards
back forward, put it in the front, put it in the back.
If you go really fast, you can,
cards will start popping out.
Those are called toppers,
and then I take those cards a lot of the time.
If they pop out right, I get the feeling.
But yeah, these are pretty simple to shuffle.
They're nice, I think the colors,
maybe a little of the colors, maybe a little bit lighter
than the actual deck, but it's still pretty, pretty cards.
So how's everyone doing today? You're all you're all here always. Okay. Oh, thank you
Are you guys fighting Radamus Prime and a J-Dog? I think no no need to fight no need to argue
We can uh, you know be friends here
Yeah, they're very pretty
And I mean basically three dollars a deck plus maybe three dollars handling or you get free shipping if you order a certain amount
But I think this, the Christina Ricci deck I got,
I think it might be genuine.
It's called Cat Full of Spiders.
Grab it back, okay, you're fine, you guys are fine.
I'll show you a picture of it if I can, let me see.
And that's Christina Ricci did a Tarot deck.
I'm also designing my Tarot deck.
I have another picture from it.
This is my recent, this is the magician I have right now.
It does pretty much look like me, this is the still the original, one of the original
pools, it looks like me a little bit, but there's another, what do you guys think?
I'll probably ask you, this is more of a cartoon style, I try to redo the Christine
It started putting making it all weird. I don't know. I think the chat CPT gets up gets confused at a certain amount of time
After you say certain amount of things do it and so I'm still working on that
But let me see if I could show you the cat full of spiders stuck. This is the cat full spiders by Christina Ricci
She was Wednesday Adams on a
That new Adams family movies cat full of spiders. Let's see
And the deck looks really cool
Yeah
So I don't know if it's gonna be the full full deck, but it's taken a while
I don't know the this Amazon tablet, it's not the best tablet. Let's see. So here we go
You can see the cover of it
Yeah, I think it's a 78 second one looks more like me. Yeah, the first one is very cartoonish
I said like almost like a Disney style animation plus fantasy the other one was a little bit more like an illustration or realistic
I'll take go through see what style I like the most. I do like the cartoonish style though the Disney style
I don't know if that's because I like my villains deck so much or
My my Disney it is a 78 car deck
Let me see. Yeah, it looks like she pretty cool. Here's another picture of it. I love the black cat right here
It's pretty cool and show you some more of the illustrations I have like this is the beat a card
The Empress I'll have to redo it in a cartoon style
It did me as a devil. It looks pretty horrifying. There's another devil card. It's not quite
Right, okay, but I'm working on it. There's my Lenore
So how are we doing? She's boiling herself. Yeah, I would buy it, but how much is it? You know, it's like
And is it like a is it like a nice dress shirt or is it like a kind of novelty shirt because you can get novelty shirts?
knockoffs
For on T move for like five bucks. Where's Joker? I haven't seen Joker in a long time. I see he's posting and stuff
So he's around. I don't know if he's
55 plus shipping a witch shipping, okay
That's you know, you know your budget, you know your budget, you know
It's a little pricey for me. I I kind of like him
Been buying my t-shirts on T move for five dollars a t-shirt. It's his white UK button with Batman shirt. Okay
Go on, go on Etsy, or no, sorry, go on a, go on Timu and look a Batman shirt and see if there's anything there though.
Might find something comparable.
Her deck is based on personal and professional journey. Yeah, Joseph.
It sounds like a great deck.
By six packs of Brutalum for 25 bucks. Yeah, my dad used to like come back with like, you know
We have like nice shoes, right? But then he would come back with this bag of like
Irregular socks and they would have something sometimes you put your foot through it
It would it wouldn't be sewn on the bottom most of the times it was there just like a little bit off
But he would always buy these are regular socks for like, you know at Ross or
real cheap they'd be real good deal, but it's like sometimes they'd be like, you know not sewn on the bottom or they'd just be like
fit really strange and
But that's where he's like to save his money on little saw
He likes to save the money on because he considered socks like something you don't really see, you know, and so it's like
You know, he was quite a he's a Gemini
quite good at
Being thrifty, but also like splurge a lot, right?
How are you guys doing?
So I want to congratulate spunky. I know spunky last night had her first show
Her channel is hey, it's spunky. I think it's hey, it's spunky like search up. Hey, it's spunky
And I'm sorry. I missed your show last night. I woke up like at 11 30
I know your shows are maybe started 10 30 last night
I woke up late and then I was I just started my show and then people are like, oh, she's still on I thought oh
Shit, I forgot but I did tell people to go check out your show subscribe to you. Hey, they're spunky. Hey, they're spunky
Shit, I don't quite remember
But uh
Let me see if I can use some more information on this cat's pulse, but I can't wait to get the deck. It sounds really cool
Yeah, if you guys are on tiktok you can go ahead and follow me on tiktok
I know I've seen some of you there you can direct message me there, which is pretty cool, right?
I think this works if I go like that. Maybe I have to put exclamation point in front of it
Yeah, I do
This is a new Nightbot command for tiktok
Yeah, maybe my night plot's not awake yet.
Oh, there we go.
It's really cool, though, over there.
I actually really like it.
I do fast-paced readings on my show there.
You know, it takes us a little bit more, I would say.
Superficial a little bit there into look. I have a nice filter on my face. So I look a little bit better there
My eyes are a little bit bigger my I don't know. I've been nice
I do have some filters on but I think I look pretty good though and
It helps out over there, you know, there's everyone's so gorgeous over there and then
But I'm doing pretty well. I am monetized on TikTok already with a membership, which is pretty cool
I made it a little bit different than this membership, but
There's private on Bolton boards and stuff back there. So if you do want more interaction and stuff like that with me
I'm not really on discord anymore
Or that's I used to be you know doing a lot of interaction there
Let me see my my laundry's done enough washing there's my link. I'll get my link pinned
I think I've been a great night.
Nice to see all you guys.
We'll have some fun hanging out.
Hopefully some people will come and say hi.
I'm talking to my chat GPT about like my show right now
and wow, I'm on the upgraded chat GPT.
But I was like asking some questions so you know that you want to know about my show
I asked me like 18 questions that are like and then every time I answer one of those questions
It has another like 20 questions
And so it is so detailed on like what it wants to know that it will really probably help help my show a lot
I say anybody with a business. Wow just talk to chat tpt about how do I do this? How do I improve this?
How do I improve this like it will honestly
It'll honestly help you it will honestly and even for free go talk to the free version of it. It will help
You can see this is Wild Car Wednesday.
We don't know where we're gonna get.
So I'll go ahead and have this panel sponsored today
because we did have a wonderful donation already.
Let me just put my, thank you.
Let me just put my Stream Artist Pins.
Go ahead and say hi.
Hopefully we have some, hey Trevor, how are you?
Trevor, are you my friend Trevor that comes on the panel?
Like I'm not sure if you're the same Trevor, but yeah yesterday when I was talking to daddy bigness
Someone came in his Trevor and then porn bombs. I'm gonna fix that episode and then
Repost it if I can I need to figure I never done it, but it's like on a stream yard
They do save your last 50 hours. Okay, so you're different Trevor. Okay. Nice. Welcome
Nice to have another Trevor here that multiple Trevor's
Um, yeah, so if anyone would like a reading anyone would like to come on panel anyone want to chat
I'm here for at least you know a while
He's using your pick. He's dangerous. Okay
Smith, I don't know. Is this true guys? What's going on here? You're gonna explain it to me. I don't quite understand
Why would Trevor be using your picture Smith your name is Smith. It's very general name
Okay guys, so let me see hi Barbara. How are you good to see ya?
Yeah, we got some mods members here. I did donate a bunch of memberships this week. I think I donated about
How many that 20
At least 10, but yeah, we've had a lot of members Wow
Of course, CrucibleGhost, if you're here, whenever CrucibleGhost gets here, he has some, yeah, Smith is lying.
CrucibleGhost has some credit on the show, I'll say.
He donated a large amount last weekend, so I want him to have some fun.
Okay, I just need to turn off my, I'll end it in a second.
Or my, uh, my washer.
Okay.
Whoo, it's set up too fast. I'm gonna come sit down again. Oh guys
This is a poor momma, okay, I'll keep an eye out now
I know the names of most of the poor mommers like I figured out like I
Seen them names multiple times by this point. So I know they don't have a easy time
Changing their accounts it seems you saw me up for this show. You should be the receipts later. Okay
Let me sit back a little bit to relax a little bit. Oh gosh
How are we doing okay
Okay
Hey, Jamie, how are you today? How are you feeling Jamie? Are you out of the hospital? Oh?
Jamie's okay. You see if I go like this. Oh
I go like this
They go like that crop then it's a little bit more crops. Okay
How's that look?
Okay, do I look really weird in these glasses? I know they're a little bit extreme. I do have my other pairs in place, but I
Think I kind of ticked our fuddies are funny that I got the two free dollar glasses
I actually went on tiktok somebody joined my chat and they're like they're wearing the same ones
They're like and they're from Hollywood. They're butchered got the weird guys all in glasses in this apartment hall. It looked like a serial killer
apartment
I'll come on up and say hi guys don't be shy. It's uh, you know
Keep me awake. I've been kind of tired lately. I've been getting a lot of sleep, but uh
You got my apartment real clean and organized got vacuumed up and your vacuum and stuff
Everything's going good. I
Love coming to say hi chatting with you guys. You guys are awesome
You're here looking at home. I'm glad to hear you're home. Oh, okay. That was good
Yeah, how are you guys doing with that with I think it's with the K with K's Barbara. I
Know I was doing the same thing. Yeah, key T. Okay like that
Yeah, if you're not on tiktok guys, it's a fun website. It's fun
I do recommend checking it out, especially because it's like a different website than YouTube and that am I ill?
Do I look ill? I'm not ill. I'm just a little tired lately
So I'm having a couple coffees. I'm not ill. I'm just normally my normal self. Hopefully. I don't look ill
I
Hopefully look healthy and and happy which I am
don't really get sick you know but you know what my ear is this ear is clogged
which is really annoying it throws off my whole balance you know my ears kind of
clogged I'm trying to oh Rodimus no no no no no I do not have any kind of viral
infection or anything like that I've actually was like a very
Disease phobic, which kept me from having really that much sex, which is bad and good. You know, I was always just very like
We I grew up in the 80s and so that was all around so it was kind of in grade though sex is very
Oh, you found me on tiktok. Okay good
Yeah, I have a cool little page there and also like it automatically makes these little shorts out of my videos and
and post it and so I have this you can just see like a little short of my regular readings and you can see it's a nice
fun thing people give little gifts and
roses and
Hearts and stuff like that and it actually they translate into a natural money. I got so some some uh
Sometimes I get like 50 cents and gifts and stuff like that after a live and that's like, you know, it's not like a lot but
I'm sure I do not I'm absolutely sure I'm held happy healthy. I'm 44 years old, you know, I'm
Just skinny. I've always been this skinny. So I
Do not have any kind of disease. Thank you mama Maria
Yeah, and so if you and also tick-tock is just fun for talking to people and you can like meet
Hot men and women like there's very attractive people there. Whatever you kind of like
It will start just like filter, you know, you'll start just getting that and then
You know, there's some very attractive people all times all types of the day and you can just meet people there
It's pretty cool
I wish I could show, yeah, there's no joke and everyone gets tested, everyone makes
sure that, you know, because it is a very treatable thing.
People don't really get AIDS anymore, they get HIV, they are able to get to non-detectable
levels with certain medications and things like that, and so it's not as big of a deal
or stigma as it was in the past, but you want to make sure you know you.
your diagnosis, so you don't inadvertently pass it on to anybody else because it is one of those things that you need to be aware of.
You can see the rainbows coming through the room. I got some beautiful time of day where the rainbows are coming through the room.
Yeah, guys. So, what is what you've been doing today? Did anybody see any interesting...
Let me see if I can share my Amazon page too.
Oh, here, okay.
I mean, this is not ready yet.
I mean, I haven't put any content on yet,
but go ahead and bookmark this page.
This is my Amazon influencer page.
And also, you might be able to figure out
how to become an influencer yourself.
If you click on that, probably a link,
it will just verify with one of your accounts
because you connect your most influential account,
I would say.
And you might qualify then you'll be able to get some
some affiliates
From Amazon or Amazon
Think I'll get better than YouTube in your opinion
Yeah, it said Trevor Ryan, okay, but yeah, it wasn't the Trevor that comes on the show
It was somebody that was copying their picture. I know it wasn't him
He's a good friend of mine. He would ruin the interview like that
Don't me put this down. Oh
Cheers guys, I got my other copy
Pretty good, I don't know if they put they put in the all the all the shots I asked because I
Seem pretty sweet, but that's okay
Also, I'm running out of cigars, so I might have to walk to the cigar place today
so
I'll see how we're doing after an hour
But yeah, beta was on I think it's Oliver Gibroni's birthday. Happy birthday Oliver Gibroni July 30th. That would make you a what Leo?
Yeah, we're in Leo season
What can I say about Leo's the rule by the Sun there are probably dog days of summer do I ever get wine drunk like beta with beta?
Um, no, but sometimes we'll be drinking at the same time. Like, uh, you know, I like to
have some twisted teas and stuff
but uh
Now I've been a little bit
tired lately
So
Have the everyone's doing great
So let's have a look at this book. I have this book. It's called the book will change your life. I
don't know. Okay, so it's
Every day it has something exciting to do, so what is this page? Let me see.
Well, mass social experience. Cut out and stick this sign on any public infrastructure you might encounter today, including when not limited to elevators, garbage trucks, cranes, foam booths, toilets, ventilation units, escalators, entrances, and subway stations. It says out of order.
Okay.
The aim is to achieve comprehensive social breakdown across the US. Okay. Well, you know, maybe not the best
They got some funny pages in here. What's this one? I just saw this body hair day or something. I mean, it's just like a great
Book to get dirty. I think this book is already can you add national body hair day?
What do you guys think about
Okay, so J-Dot unknown fatigue
Yeah, that's what I have you're in the ER. There's people there for that. I know I've had that I don't know what it is
I just been getting sleepy
And
I'm drinking a couple copies. I'll probably like fall right back down and go to sleep again
You know, but I have I have like the dryer going. It's kind of hypnotic. Hopefully it's not mono. I haven't really kissed anybody
so I
Don't know how I get that but
Courtney love has a good song called mono. You want to check it out? It's called Courtney love mono
Is it the part in the book that you wrote where I had it
Had to come and save the day. Did you miss me?
You got mono from a chick once they put you out for a month. Oh my gosh, I
Hopefully I don't have it
Yeah, I haven't heard of that for a while too
I'm just a little tired today and I was yesterday too you could tell I fell asleep so
But I've been drinking a lot less lately though that's pretty good
Seems like it's a little quiet right now. So I think I might come back in a little bit
I'll be back probably by eight o'clock tonight
Little bit early you guys can go check out beta or summer or whoever else is on I love you guys
I'll be back in a little bit. It's gonna close my eyes for a little bit and I'll be back
Love ya